<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hazy Skye</title>
    <description>Hazy Skye</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>One Flew Over The Lil Jeep</title>
        <description>
          
          Just keep seeing you in my mind’s eye Lil Peep, my baby Gustav, why’d you have to die? Why oh why was it you and not I? Life isn’t fair but I have to learn to not mind. All I know is I’m a Crybaby and we’re out of line....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-one-flew-over-the-lil-jeep/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-one-flew-over-the-lil-jeep/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crave</title>
        <description>
          
          In times of sorrow built around your problems, you begin to bleed and beg for a new understanding around you but for the solution you’re not willing to work at finding suffering in chaos that you demanded and now act like a reprieve is what you need when to see...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 08:04:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-crave/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-crave/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Devil Sight</title>
        <description>
          
          I used to see through the devil’s eyes Now I see right through him and evil lies Popped each pill like I was ready to die Yet came the day, finally I wanted to fly Like a caged bird with no way out Couldn’t fathom a new escape route I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 07:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-devil-sight/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-devil-sight/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Laterally Evolving</title>
        <description>
          
          In this moment of time, I search for peace without you Always numbing myself with the drugs of today Lookin’ for the drugs of tomorrow Realisin’ it is both the pain and symptoms of a grand delusion we share together Only in changing ourselves can we ever hope to be...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 07:42:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-laterally-evolving/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-laterally-evolving/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My Virtue Is Bleeding</title>
        <description>
          
          My virtue is bleeding, living this life, the devil deceives me Fuck a bitch when she bleedin, not the kind of time I’m heedin Doin drugs in back of the club and cut her arm screamin’ Droppin pills in my hennesy, touchin her, pretend for Peep that I’m Lil Kennedy...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2019 03:58:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-my-virtue-is-bleeding/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-26-my-virtue-is-bleeding/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <description>
          
          Welcome to Hazy Skye’s personal website dedicated to her life in poetry. More content will be added as it becomes available.

        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 08:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2019-11-25-welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2019-11-25-welcome/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
